If you want really
fast feedback on a
title or an idea
when you're ideating, all
you need to do
is go over to
the AI, click on
guardrails and ask, is
this a good idea?
What it's going to
do, it's going to
check out your idea
based on the information
you've loaded into the
brain and compare it
against that. Then it's
going to come back
with information about how
in line it might
be with the data
you fed it. And
it's going to score
it like this. It's
going to look at
if it might relate
to the three problems,
and it's going to
make sure it's in
line with the top
of your umbrella, which
is how you're going
to position your channel
business and offer. And
then it's going to
give you some rough
title ideas. But wait,
please, for the love
of cute puppies, I
am begging you, don't
use these titles just
because AI suggested them.
These are examples to
inspire you. Sometimes they
might be good, but
most of the time
they're going to use
weird words. This is
not God. This is
an AI I built
that is very good,
but it's not there
to replace your brain
or what you're doing.
It's going to give
you some rough title
ideas. But wait, please,
what you learn in
the pattern bank. You
can also just give
it a rough kind
of idea about a
sort of video you
want to make, and
it's going to help
you work out if
you should even make
it. All right, cool.
That's it. Move on
to the next video.